Hello.
こんにちは
It's beautiful.
綺麗ですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
When I heard about your occupation, I felt like I was right.
なんか、ご職業聞いてやっぱりなって感じですけど
Oh?
あ、ですか?
Almost Mr.
ほぼさん
I love children.
子供が大好き
子供大好きです
Well then, it's time to change jobs.
じゃあ、転職ですね
That's right, changing jobs.
そうですね、転職
Boys definitely cry, right?
男の子とかはやっぱり泣くでしょ
That's right, a one-of-a-kind child.
そうですね、ワンパクな子が
I bully girls.
女の子をいじめるし
There are also human relationships, like with parents.
人間関係とかもありますよな、親御さんとかね
Colleagues and teachers.
同僚の先生とか
結構最近、
It seems that there are also things like power parents.
パ ワーパレンズとかそういうのもいるみたいですね
It's quite difficult.
結構大変ですね
Or rather, do you have any male colleagues?
ほぼさんというか、 同僚で男の人もいるんですか?
sometimes.
たまに
After all, that's true.
やっぱりそうですよね
The same goes for nurses, but there aren't many of them.
看護師もそうですけど、少ないですよね
Mr. Hobo is here today.
そんなほぼさんが、 今日ここにいらしたわけですけれども、
You know what it's going to do.
それは何やるか分かってますよね
I agree.
そうですね
That means you are not a child's partner.
子供の相手ではないということですね
I'm dealing with an adult though.
大人の相手ですけど
Do you like it, that kind of thing?
好きですか、そういうことは?
I agree.
そうですね
I wonder if I like him as much as other people.
人並みには好きな方なのかな
got it.
わかりました
Is there anyone who does this often?
しょっちゅうする人はいるんですか?
Yeah.
うん
got it.
わかりました
That's good, isn't it?
いいですよね
Single is single, right?
独身は独身ですよね?
I'm single.
独身です
If I were a mother, I would want to have many children.
もし母親にやったらたくさん子供が欲しい、
Is it something like that?
みたいな感じですか?
I agree.
そうですね
Isn't it a lot of manual labor?
ほぼさんって、 肉体労働じゃないですか、
I think it's free labor, but do you sleep on your days off?
自由労働だと思いますけど、 お休みの日とか寝ちゃいます?
I agree.
そうですね
I think I often sleep exhausted.
ぐったり寝ていることが多いかなと
Wake up, clean, do laundry, etc.
起きて掃除洗濯をやって、 そうですね
Things like house and bills.
家のこととか、支払いとかね
various.
い ろいろ
It goes by so quickly, isn't it?
あっという間ですよね
It goes by so quickly.
あっという間です
I'm young and my skin seems to be tight,
若くて、肌がピチピチしてそうですけど、
Isn't the style nice too?
スタイルもいいんじゃないですか、
you.
あなたは
is that so.
そう ですか
Where is your charm point?
チャームポイントはどこですか?
Is it a charm point?
チャームポイントですか?
Even though it's a group date, I'm confident here.
合コンとか言って、私、ここは自信あります
Are there lungs in your chest?
胸に肺があるの?
Confidence.
自信が
Breast shape?
胸の形?
Is there a needle in your chest?
胸に針があるんですか?
I wonder if it's a good thing.
いい方なのかなって
In other words, beautiful breasts,
つまり、美乳っていうことですね、
In other words.
つまりは
I agree.
そうですね
He is a beautiful father to his family.
家族に美しい父ということです
I got it.
かしこまりました
Well then, I would like to enjoy my beautiful father to the fullest.
じゃあ、その美しい父をいっぱい堪能したいと思います
Is that okay?
それ大丈夫ですかね?
I don't look like a girl, but I do things like that.
女の子には見えないんですけど、そういうことをやる
Is it true?
本当 ですか?
It's like wearing a loose sweatshirt and going to a karaoke bar in your neighborhood.
ラフなスウェット着て、 近所のカラオケ屋さんにも行くような
Although it feels like it.
感じ ですけども
It's true, isn't it?
本当ですよね
That's true.
本当ですね
It might be embarrassing if I did that, but
そうしましたら、恥ずかしいかもしれませんけども、
It can be worn as underwear from above or below.
上からでも下からでも、 サクッと下着になっていただいて良い
Is it?
ですか?
I just stood there and set it aside for a moment.
ちょっと、 立たんで横に置いていただ
Stay.
いて
As I said earlier, this is a beautiful shop.
先 ほど言っていた、 これが美しい屋なんですけど、
I can't see it yet, but it looks like it's in good shape.
まだ見えてはませんけど、 形が良さそうですね
How many cups should I use?
何カップにやるんですか?
It's T.
Tです
I don't want people to think I'm a pervert, but
変態とか思われたら嫌なんですけど、
I have an armpit fetish.
脇の下フェチなんですけども
Armpit?
脇の下?
Ah, beautiful.
あ、綺麗
It's been processed properly, beautifully.
ちゃんと処理されてるんですよ、綺麗に
For the time being, I am doing the following.
一応処理の方は、 するようにしています
Can I disagree?
反対もいいですか?
Is it okay to do the opposite?
反対も大丈夫かな?
After all, if it didn't have a name, it would come in, right?
や っぱり名前なかったら入ってきますよね、
that.
それ
It's coming in.
それ入ってきます
The style is also good.
スタイルも良い
Please make sure your waist is cinched in and you can stand up a little.
ウエストもちゃんとくびれって、 ちょっと立っていただいて良い
Is it?
ですか?
It's thin, after all.
細 いですね、やっぱ
Is it thin?
細いんですかね
The waist is also 56?
ウエストも56?
I wonder what it is?
どうなんだろう?
I've never measured it.
測ったことないです
Is the back also on the floor?
後ろも床ですか?
It's subtle, but it's also a small butt.
微妙だけど、微尻でもありますね
Won't you tell me, dear?
言われませんか、あなた?
You won't be told.
言われないですよ
A female co-worker asked me, ``Don't tell me if your butt is pretty.''
同僚の女の人から、あなた、 お尻がきれいなのか言わないで
please.
ください
I'll just touch it and put it underground.
ちょっと 触って、 地下にしちゃいますけど
Please face me for a moment.
ちょっと僕に正面に向いていただいて
Meet me underground?
地下に会います?
I won't meet you.
会いません
Won't you meet me?
会いません?
What would you do if something like this happened to you on the train?
電車でこんなことしてきたら、 どう しますか、
My father?
親父が?
I don't like it.
嫌です
How do you get rid of it?
どうやって退治しますか?
This person is usually different.
普通に、この人違うんですよ
All I can do is say.
言うぐらいしかできない
It's a bit of a small butt.
ちょっと微尻ですね
Well then, please turn towards me.
じゃあ、クルッとか 私の方に向いていただいて
You can stand or sit, but
立っていても座っていてもいいんですけど、
If you can show me something beautiful from above or below,
上からでも下からでも 美しいものを見せてもらえれば
I think so.
と思います
Shall we go from above?
上 から行きますか?
From above?
上から?
Its beautiful.
その美しい
Is the bottom okay too?
下もいいですか?
Then, Hobo-san, you made an M-shape,
そしたら、 ほぼさん、 M字になっていただいて、
You can lean on it.
よりかかっていいですよ
From below the knees, both arms.
膝の下から、両腕
So, you open your pussy yourself.
で、おまんこを自分で開くってやつですね
With a click.
パクッと
I think this is my first experience.
初めての経験だと思いますけど
Who ever told you to do something like this?
今までこんなことやれなんて言った人?
No.
ないです
I've never been told that.
言われたことない
It's curved nicely.
綺麗に反ってらっしゃるんですね
Can I open my legs too?
足も開いていいですか?
Yes, beautiful.
はい、綺麗
How many men have worshiped this?
これを拝んだ男性は何人いますか?
I don't know.
分かんない
male.
男性
About 3 people.
3人くらい
Ah, there aren't many.
あ、少ないですね
I'm the 4th person.
僕4人目
Can you open your legs a little more?
もうちょっと足開けますか?
The beautiful uncle I mentioned earlier.
さっき言った美しいおじちが
Can I see your uncle?
おじちを見せてもらっていいですか?
The needle.
針が
If I do that, can I be the fourth one?
そうしましたら、4つ目になっていただいていいですか?
Point my ass.
僕のお尻を向けて
Also the tail.
尾尻も
It's a beautiful butt, after all.
美尻ですよ、やっぱ
the law of nature.
り
Can you open your legs for a moment?
ちょっと 足を開いていいですか?
This one too.
こっちも
Can you show your face from the right side?
顔を右側から出せます?
Show me your face.
顔を見せて
From the right side.
右側から
Does it feel good here?
ここは気持ちいいですか?
Are you aware of your erogenous body?
性感体って自分で自覚してます?
I don't know.
分かんない
Does it feel good here?
ここは気持ちいいですか?
You actually have beautiful needles.
本当は美しい針がありますね
Do you like fierce or gentle?
激しいのと優しいのが好きですか?
Oh no, you should be kinder.
やばい、優しい方が
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
Did I say it?
言っちゃった?
Say it again.
もう一回言ってごらん
That's a lot of sweat.
すごい汗ですね
Please lie down here.
こっちに寝てごらん
こ っちに寝てごらん
Please lie down here.
こっちに寝てごらん
No, no.
違う違う
Try lying down.
横に寝てごらん
Open your legs.
足を開けて
Hold your leg with your left hand.
左手で足を抱えてごらん
Show me even if you haven't done it.
やったことなくても見せて
Come on out if it feels good.
気持ちいいとか出てごらん
Touch my dick with your right hand.
右手でチンチン触って
On the other side too.
反対側も
Do you want to lick it?
舐めたい?
Lick it.
舐めてごらん
Are you tired?
疲れちゃった?
I'm tired.
疲れちゃった
While touching the bag with my left hand.
左手で袋を触りながら
In front of your feet.
足の前に
Hold your own feet.
自分で足を抱えてごらん
both.
両方
Please hold my leg once.
一回足を抱えてごらん
It's difficult to put in.
入れるの難しい
Spit out your teeth.
歯を吐いて
Was today's Instacts Go?
今日のインスタクトスゴーでした?
It feels amazing.
すごい気持ちいい